<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="icebreakers_exercise_description">Practice greetings in realistic everyday situations.
Get a scenario, formulate your response, and  and get used to starting conversations with anyone comfortably
Get a scenario, formulate your response, and get used to starting conversations with anyone comfortably</string>
    <string name="what_to_say_next_exercise_description">Practice keeping conversations alive in real-life situations.
        Read a short scenario and come up with your own natural response to stay engaged and connect better.
</string>
    <string name="finish_the_thought_exercise_description">You’ll get a typical sentence opener — your task is to finish it naturally,
        as if you\'re in a real situation. It could be a short story, a comment,
        or a follow-up question — whatever helps you build your communicative reflexes and stay confident in a dialogue</string>
    <string name="the_key_to_small_talk_exercise_description">Train yourself to respond in a more interesting and meaningful way — not just with one-word answers.
In this exercise, you’ll get common questions like “Where are you from?” or “How was your day?” — and your task is not just to answer, but to add something of your own: a detail, a joke,
        or a follow-up question. It helps you keep the conversation going instead of cutting it short</string>
    <string name="dating_route_exercise_description">Imagine you\'re new in a group of unfamiliar people. Throughout the day, you find yourself
        in different situations: standing in line for coffee, sitting at a shared lunch table, or
        waiting for a meeting to begin. In each of these moments, your task is to initiate a
        conversation — start with a phrase, make a comment, or ask a question.
This exercise helps you practice the skill of confidently starting conversations, overcome awkwardness, find your own communication style, and adapt more easily to a new social environment.</string>
    <string name="farewell_remark_exercise_description">In this exercise, you\'ll practice ending conversations naturally and appropriately.
You\'ll get a short description of a situation where it\'s time to say goodbye — whether in a friendly, formal,
        or slightly humorous tone, depending on the context. Imagine you\'re really in that moment, and your final line is the lasting impression you leave.
        This practice helps you confidently wrap up a conversation — smoothly, without awkwardness, and with a pleasant aftertaste.</string>
    <string name="tongue_twisters_easy_exercise_description">Practice simple tongue twisters to improve your pronunciation and fluency.
Repeat fun and easy tongue twisters to warm up your speech muscles and build clear, confident articulation.
</string>
    <string name="word_spirit_exercise_description">Name as many nouns, adjectives, or verbs as you can in 60 seconds to sharpen your word recall and thinking speed
</string>
</resources>